The machine learning workflow is always following these steps.
First, we need to frame the problem.
What are we trying to achieve here?
Why? Who cares about this problem?
Do we even need machine learning?
Once we have answered this question,
we need to focus on data.
How much data do we need?
Is it easy to obtain?
How much processing is required?
When our data set is ready,
we can focus on the model.
Which approach is best for this problem?
What are the constraints?
For example, are limited because of the hardware?
We then have a feedback loop between data and model.
We can use the model predictions to decide if we need more data or not for example.
Let's go back to the traffic sign data set.
In this machine learning problem,
we are trying to classify traffic signs just by using images.
The available data, consisting thousands of images for each type of traffic sign.
As for the model, we will experiment with different algorithm,
such as logistic regression and neural networks.